Karltun Moreno

"I am a Full Stack Web Developer that lives and breathes digital media practices in order to find solutions for mobile first web development applications (clients). This allows me to conduct a professional business that champions the expansion of new and existing brands." Specializing in React.js, Javascript, Express and Mysql. https://github.com/karltunmoreno/My-Portfoliohttps://github.com/karltunmoreno

EXPERIENCE

Vauhlt - Miami, FL. Front End Developer October 2022 - Present

Created agile UI-UX web development in Next.js/React. This is a personal wallet for individual blockchain trading, purchasing and storing crypto assets and alike. Beta testing front-end to back-end accounting. Apex Chart, Node Sass, React Bootstrap, React-Perfect-Scrollbar, Typescript, CSS HTML, Github. https://karltunmoreno.github.io/Vauhlt/

Karltun Moreno 360 - Los Angeles, CA.

Full Stack Web Developer January 2022 - Present

Developed a full stack website with service pages, bookings, appointments, contact email form, fully mobile responsive app. Website for real estate content services. Used Matterport 3D, drones, video, Javascript, JQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Photoshop, Final Cut Pro, Adobe Premiere & machine learning GPT. www.karltunmoreno360.com

Manuel Rodando - Miami, FL.

Full Stack Web Developer

June 2022 - Present

Built a SPA, UI-UX for You Tube personality on social media platform with blog travel and talk show site. Linked DNS endpoints, setup domain Go Daddy, Used Adobe Dreamweaver, Photoshop, HTML,CSS, Bootstrap, VS Code, GitHub. www.manuelrodando.com

Outer Bounds Pictures - Los Angeles, CA.

Full Stack Web Developer - CEO

April 2016 - Present

Designed a full stack website with service pages, bookings, appointments, contact email form, fully mobile responsive site with e-commerce art store. Visa, Master Card and Square payments setup. Photography, video services, apparel site. Used Javascript, JQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Photoshop, Final Cut Pro, Adobe Premiere & machine learning GPT. www.outerboundspictures.com

EDUCATION

University of Miami, Coral Gables, FL.

Technical Certificate: Full Stack Web Development in Coding Javascript & Full Stack Development in MERN Stack. California State University (CSUN), Northridge, CA.

Bachelor in Psychology Studied Behavioral Science.

CONTACT

6911 Remmet Ave #208
Canoga Park, CA. 91303
(818)317-4178
Karltunmoreno@gmail.com
www.linkedin.com/in/ karltunmoreno-0a910a46/

SKILLS

DRONE - UAS PART 107 CERTIFIED PHOTOGRAPHY - MATTERPORT 3D EDITING - VISUAL MEDIA GRAPHIC DESIGN BUDGETING & SCHEDULING GOOGLE SEARCH CENTRAL

FRONT END LANGUAGES

REACT.JS - NEXT. JS - IONIC - REDUX
ADOBE DREAMWEAVER
HTML - CSS
GIT HUB
JAVASCRIPT - TYPESCRIPT

BOOTSTRAP JQUERY - AJAX - JSON

BACK END

NODE.JS
EXPRESS.JS, MVC
SQL / MYSQL/ ORM
HEROKU / JAWSDB
INSOMNIA / REST- API's (CRUD)
MONGO DB / MONGOOSE / ATLAS / ODM
APOLLO / GRAPHQL - API

SOFTWARE

POWER POINT / WORD / EXCEL ADOBE PHOTOSHOP ADOBE LIGHTROOM ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR & XD, FIGMA ADOBE PREMIERE PRO ADOBE AFTER EFFECTS ADOBE ACROBAT

MORE WEB PROJECTS

Food Fest - PWA- Html, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, Chrome Dev tools, Github. Application for quick offline uploading. Mobile UI responsive with home screen. Front-end stack. https://karltunmoreno.github.io/Food-Fest/Animal List Administrator - Rest Api, CRUD funtions, Javascript, Html, CSS, Node.js, Express.js. https:afternooncaverns-57263.herokuapp.com/Just Geeky News - MVC - Javascript,

Node.js, MySql, Express.js. https://protectedlowlands-09239.herokuapp.com/ **Momentuum** - React.js,

Javascript, Html, CSS, Node.js.

https://karltunmoreno.github.io/nomentuum/ **Task Manager** - Html, CSS Javascript, Bootstrap, JQuery. https://karltunmoreno.github.io/Task-Manager/